

Profile

Al Researcher and Embedded Software Developer skillful in design, installation, testing and maintenance of complex hardware/software systems. Experienced with the modern math modeling technologies and machine learning methods. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Lecturer at ITMO University

September 2022 — December 2022

Implementation of Python Programming course for 1st Grade university students.

Founder / CEO at Omnitech LLC

March 2022

Implementation of Human-Machine interaction platform based on hand position modeling using muscle activity tracking.

Lab Assistant / Lecturer at ITMO University

February 2022 — June 2022

Implementation of Object Oriented Programming course for 2nd Grade university students.

Senior Research Assistant at ITMO University

March 2022 — June 2022

Research of improving the reliability of sign language processing in cases of limited datasets.

Senior Research Assistant at ITMO University

February 2021 — June 2021

Research of Few-Shot Machine Learning solutions for Sign Language interpretation.

Hardware Team Lead at ITKvar LLC

April 2020 — August 2021

Implementation of portable DSP based Sign Language processing unit. Created unique portable device for real time interpretation of hand gestures based on analysis of muscle activity.

Hardware Developer at ITKvar LLC

March 2019 — April 2020

Hardware and Software implementation of portable Electromyography (EMG) acquisition circuit. DSP algorithms development, processing of data obtained during EMG measurements.

Details

+79126876603 bedewyrm@gmail.com

Skills

Data Analysis

Creative Thinking

Strong Communication Skills

Languages

English

Russian

French

Education

ITMO University, St. Petersburg
Faculty of Information Technologies and Programming

★ Professional Awards

Intel ISEF

2018

4th Grand Award in Embedded Systems

Intel ISEF

2019

2nd Grand Award in Systems Software

Google Science Fair

2019

Winner

Lego Builder Award

2019

Winner

★ Publications

Support for communication with deaf and dumb patients via Few-Shot Machine Learning

2021

15th Multi-Conference on Computer Science and Information Systems, MCCSIS 2021, 2021, pp. 216-220

Improving Sign Language Processing via Few-Shot Machine Learning

2022

Scientific and Technical Journal of Information Technologies, Mechanics and Optics, 2022, Vol. 22, No. 3(139), pp. 559-566

Courses

Idea to Market, Stanford

August 2021 — December 2021